== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
(Sheldon:)Cohabitation
with my girlfriend?
(Sheldon:)That's a great deal
to process.
(Leonard:)Mm.
(Leonard:)It's only for five weeks.
(Penny:)Yeah, and we'll be
right across the hall.
(Amy:)What do you think?
(Sheldon:)I don't know.
(Sheldon:)What if living together
kills the romance?
(Penny:)Okay, you guys had sex
one whole time.
(Penny:)Nothing can put out
a fire like that.
(Sheldon:)Yeah, but what happens
(Sheldon:)when we each get a peek
behind the curtain?
(Sheldon:)I mean, she's never even
seen me unshaven.
(Leonard:)You just shaved yesterday.
(Leonard:)You're good for three months.
(Amy:)Sheldon, I understand
your apprehension,
(Amy:)but let me appeal
to the scientist in you.
(Amy:)Given the five-week end date,
(Amy:)isn't it the perfect opportunity
to consider this an experiment
(Amy:)and collect data
on our compatibility?
(Sheldon:)Don't try luring me in
with sexy talk.
(Penny:)Okay.
Star Trek:
The Original Series.
The Enterprise was
on a five-year mission
(Leonard:)to explore new worlds.
(Leonard:)Think of this
as your